indiacatalog.com 2016-03-05

# India Catalog - Marketplace for Indian Businesses - Privacy Statement

### Collecting information

In general, you can visit this site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you and to tell you what we plan to do with that information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have personally identifiable information used for further contact with you, we will do our best to respect your wishes. If you sign up to receive an electronic newsletter or enter your name on an email list, each message will include instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from that list. 

In order to improve our Web site and collect reader profile information, we may ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products and contact preferences. We use this information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service. You can choose not to supply us with your personal information. In that case, you can still visit most of this site, but you may not be able to access certain offers and services.

IndiaCatalog.com collects information on the domains, IP addresses and Web browsers from which people visit our site. We use this data to track trends in our site traffic and for making improvements. This information is collected on an aggregate basis and is not associated with a particular individual.

### Linking to other Web sites

This site contains links to other Web sites. IndiaCatalog.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content, accuracy or opinions expressed on such Web sites, and such Web sites are not investigated, monitored or checked by us for accuracy or completeness. Inclusion of any linked Web site on our site does not imply approval or endorsement of the linked Web site by us. 

### Using cookies 

IndiaCatalog.com may use cookies on some Web site pages to help us serve you better. Cookies enable us to provide you with a more valuable experience by telling us which areas of the Web site are of most interest to you. 

You can set your browser to warn you before you collect a cookie. If you choose to disable cookies in your browser, you can still access most of our Web site but you may be unable to experience all the site’s features and functionality.

### Asking questions

We welcome comments and questions about our privacy statement. Because of the rapidly evolving nature of the Internet, we reserve the right to change this statement at any time. Direct your privacy questions to [feedback@indiacatalog.com](mailto:feedback@indiacatalog.com)
